// Questions for the quiz
const questions = [
    {
        question: "Which of the animals is the biggest?",
        answers: ["Mouse", "Horse", "Elephant", "Lion"],
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the capital city of Finland?",
        answers: ["Helsinki", "Paris", "Tokyo", "Stockholm"],
        correct: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "What does Au stand for in the periodic table?",
        answers: ["Silver", "Gold", "Sodium", "Argon"],
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the capital city of Iceland?",
        answers: ["Prague", "Reykjavik", "Vilnius", "Berlin"],
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Who played James Bond in the film Casino Royale(2006)?",
        answers: ["Sean Connery", "Roger Moore", "Daniel Craig", "Timothy Dalton"],
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the original author of Dracula?",
        answers: ["Bram Stoker", "Robert Louis Stevenson", "Daphne du Maurier", "Stephen King"],
        correct: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Which painter painted The Scream?",
        answers: ["Vincent van Gogh", "Leonardo Da Vinci", "Paul Gauguin", "Edvard Munch"],
        correct: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "Which group performed the song Run to the Hills?",
        answers: ["Metallica", "Anthrax", "Iron Maiden", "AC/DC"],
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Which group performed the song A Hard Day's Night?",
        answers: ["The Beatles", "Queen", "Beach Boys", "Eagles"],
        correct: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Where could you see Diocletian's Palace?",
        answers: ["Denmark", "Italy", "Croatia", "Austria"],
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the biggest state in USA?",
        answers: ["Alaska", "Texas", "California", "Florida"],
        correct: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Where could you see Christ the Redeemer?",
        answers: ["Finland", "Mexico", "Canada", "Brazil"],
        correct: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following artists has the most Grammy wins?",
        answers: ["Beyonce", "Jay-z", "John Williams", "Bruce Springsteen"],
        correct: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following artists has the most Grammy nominations?",
        answers: ["Eminem", "Alicia Keys", "Stevie Wonder", "Kanye West"],
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "How fast is the speed of sound in air?",
        answers: ["735 km/h", "1235 km/h", "2100 km/h", "1870 km/h"],
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Where could you see the Spanish Steps?",
        answers: ["Spain", "Greece", "Italy", "Germany"],
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the population of China (2018)?",
        answers: ["1,4 billion", "900 million", "2,1 billion", "1,9 billion"],
        correct: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the birds is the biggest?",
        answers: ["Penguin", "Ostrich", "Bald Eagle", "Emu"],
        correct: "d"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the freezing point of ethanol?",
        answers: ["-240 째C", "-49 째C", "-114 째C", "-424 째C"],
        correct: "c"
    }
]